Yes, ma'am.
cats
All cats.
It's all I have.
Thank you very much.
Here it comes.
I'm filming it on YouTube.
Yuu's contacts today.
Put them in the eyeglass case.
Put her contacts next to the eyeglass case.
Put them firmly next to my bag
I probably forgot it.
So today
Glasses life
Vegetable life
phew!
Zuzukore!
Cute!
Please put popcorn in it!
Next time
We have a regular black cat.
Oh, that cat is adorable.
That's a gold one.
Blue eyes.
This one's called Kotaro.
He's a bit of a surprise.
And this one?
Blue eyes.
Blue eyes?
Wait a minute.
Don't go bald.
Don't be bald?
I don't care.
Why is this the cat's job?
Here.
What's that?
Here we go.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Okay, okay.
Fireflies, look over there.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Thank you very much.
Crank it up?
Crank it up.
Crank it up!
Thank you very much for watching.
Today is the first shoot since I cut my hair.
I cut my hair yesterday.
Do you know why?
What? What? What? What what?
The correct answer is that your hair is damaged.
My hair looks like this.
It looks like something Gao would wear.
He's cute.
It's the least animalistic.
Like blue.
Ah, beautiful surgery.
Yes, thank you.
Tenkyan
Thank you, Marizo Map.
What foot?
Aah! What?
That's scary!
Marizo.
They're attacking us.
Marizo is awesome.
ED.
Oh, are they small fry?
Thank you for watching!
Oh no!
Animals
Zookeeper.
There are animals.
There are all kinds of animals
I'm not a keeper.
They were all given to Mr. Kobayashi.
I'm scared.
That's my food!
Gather around
Let's do our own animal poses!
Haisukin
Someone's lost.
I don't have any.
You don't have it.
Let's try one.
Great.
I'll give it a shot.
Go to the middle.
It's all there, though.
Thank you for watching.
Then what land did you show them.
At first glance you might think that I don't know what kind of animal dish I am cooking because there are so many animals, but in fact, here is the box.
I was a fox.
Here is Mayang Maan, the manager of the Ebichu Zoo.
I'm going to make rough money with animals!
On the back ground, on the back ground of the zoo.
I mean, the whole zoo is in full view.
I, tiger and cat, am here.
My nose is too pinched.
I was eating curry.
But I couldn't taste it.
I don't know...
I drank a latte and it tasted like water.
I really didn't feel anything.
Really?
I felt the curry.
That's good.
I guess we're both animals.
A cat.
A cat tiger?
Pose as a cat tiger, please.
Okay.
Big belly.
He's got a fish in his mouth!
That's awesome!
That wasn't so bad.
I got a fish.
Nice bath!
Yes!
It's cold.
It's cold in the air
Itchy, itchy, itchy
Itchy, itchy
The cat has it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I don't know if I can lose.
That's cute.
Mama's Peace
Fourteen years old.
How old is
You're in the year of the tiger.
No, not tiger years.
You don't have a dragon.
A properly good one.
I wonder if I can find one.
Good work, sir.
Thanks for your time
Thank you very much
I ate a chocolate chip.
You'll eat it.
I'll eat it with you.
We ate it together.
Don't eat it. You'll take the lip off.
It's coming off like crazy.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes, sir.
I'll have my dinner first.
Damn.
You know what?
What kind of rock-paper-scissors-scissors game was that?
Who'll eat lunch first?
Who gets to eat lunch first?
When this is over, we'll start filming.
Oh, it's lunch time.
I lost.
Hi, Izamiyashi.
Shut up, you look like you want it!
Thanks, Izamiyashi.
Shut up, he wants it!
lan This
from this
hmm
I'm going to walk here.
I'm off.
Good morning
Good morning.
We're in the middle of the making-of, the live photo shoot.
Not "making of." We're in the middle of a photo shoot.
I can't wait until the next dinner.
I'm eating chocolate stick bread.
It's delicious.
For the first time today.
I'm wearing my notebook hat.
It's the sky, isn't it?
With a natural disrespect.